[
    { "question" : "كَتَبَ", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/kataba/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "قَرَأَ", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "/qara'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "شَرِبَ", "answer" : "to drink", "pronunciation" : "/shariba/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَكَلَ", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "/akala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "فَعَلَ", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/fa'ala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "رَأَى", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/ra'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "قَالَ", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/qala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَتَى", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/ata/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ذَهَبَ", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/dahaba/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "جَاءَ", "answer" : "to arrive", "pronunciation" : "/jaa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "نَظَرَ", "answer" : "to look", "pronunciation" : "/nazara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "عَمِلَ", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/amila/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "سَمِعَ", "answer" : "to hear", "pronunciation" : "/sami'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "رَحَلَ", "answer" : "to travel", "pronunciation" : "/rahala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "خَرَجَ", "answer" : "to go out", "pronunciation" : "/kharaja/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "فَهِمَ", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "/fahima/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "شَاهَدَ", "answer" : "to watch", "pronunciation" : "/shahada/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "حَضَرَ", "answer" : "to attend", "pronunciation" : "/hadara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "تَكَلَّمَ", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/takallama/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "دَرَسَ", "answer" : "to study", "pronunciation" : "/darasa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ذَكَرَ", "answer" : "to mention", "pronunciation" : "/dhakara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "تَعَلَّمَ", "answer" : "to learn", "pronunciation" : "/ta'allama/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَعْطَى", "answer" : "to give", "pronunciation" : "/a'tha/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "تَذَكَّرَ", "answer" : "to remember", "pronunciation" : "/tadhakkara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَخَذَ", "answer" : "to take", "pronunciation" : "/akhadha/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَرَادَ", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/arada/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "حَصَلَ", "answer" : "to happen", "pronunciation" : "/hasala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "نَامَ", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "/nama/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "رَكِبَ", "answer" : "to ride", "pronunciation" : "/rakiba/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "جَرَى", "answer" : "to run", "pronunciation" : "/jara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "أَنْتَجَ", "answer" : "to produce", "pronunciation" : "/antaja/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "وَضَعَ", "answer" : "to put", "pronunciation" : "/wada'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "اِسْتَمَتَعَ", "answer" : "to enjoy", "pronunciation" : "/istamata'a/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "اِسْتَخْدَمَ", "answer" : "to use", "pronunciation" : "/istakhdam/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "تَوَقَّفَ", "answer" : "to stop", "pronunciation" : "/tawaqqafa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "حَاوَلَ", "answer" : "to try", "pronunciation" : "/hawala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "اِحْتَفَلَ", "answer" : "to celebrate", "pronunciation" : "/ihtafala/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "اِعْتَذَرَ", "answer" : "to apologize", "pronunciation" : "/i'thazara/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "اِنْتَهَى", "answer" : "to finish", "pronunciation" : "/intaha/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ماء", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/māʾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شمس", "answer" : "sun", "pronunciation" : "/shams/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "بيت", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/bayt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "طعام", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/ṭaʿām/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "يد", "answer" : "hand", "pronunciation" : "/yad/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "وقت", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "/waqt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "عين", "answer" : "eye", "pronunciation" : "/ʿayn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "كلمة", "answer" : "word", "pronunciation" : "/kalimah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شجرة", "answer" : "tree", "pronunciation" : "/shajarah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "دم", "answer" : "blood", "pronunciation" : "/dam/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "مدينة", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/madīnah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "صوت", "answer" : "sound", "pronunciation" : "/ṣawt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "رجل", "answer" : "man", "pronunciation" : "/rajul/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "بنت", "answer" : "girl", "pronunciation" : "/bint/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "حجر", "answer" : "stone", "pronunciation" : "/ḥajar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "حليب", "answer" : "milk", "pronunciation" : "/ḥalīb/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "باب", "answer" : "door", "pronunciation" : "/bāb/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "سماء", "answer" : "sky", "pronunciation" : "/samāʾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "سفر", "answer" : "travel", "pronunciation" : "/safar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "دولة", "answer" : "country", "pronunciation" : "/dawlah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "قلب", "answer" : "heart", "pronunciation" : "/qalb/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "رياح", "answer" : "wind", "pronunciation" : "/ryāḥ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "حق", "answer" : "right", "pronunciation" : "/ḥaqq/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "نار", "answer" : "fire", "pronunciation" : "/nār/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "زمن", "answer" : "era", "pronunciation" : "/zaman/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "كتاب", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "/kitāb/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ملك", "answer" : "king", "pronunciation" : "/malik/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "دنيا", "answer" : "world", "pronunciation" : "/dunyā/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "قمر", "answer" : "moon", "pronunciation" : "/qamar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "بحر", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "/baḥr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "جنس", "answer" : "gender", "pronunciation" : "/jins/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "صحة", "answer" : "health", "pronunciation" : "/ṣiḥḥah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ملابس", "answer" : "clothes", "pronunciation" : "/milābis/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "عربة", "answer" : "cart", "pronunciation" : "/ʿarabah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شمعة", "answer" : "candle", "pronunciation" : "/shamʿah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "زهرة", "answer" : "flower", "pronunciation" : "/zahrāh/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "جبل", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "/jabal/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "عطر", "answer" : "perfume", "pronunciation" : "/ʿitr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شماريخ", "answer" : "fireworks", "pronunciation" : "/shumārīkh/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "قلم", "answer" : "pen", "pronunciation" : "/qalam/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "رمل", "answer" : "sand", "pronunciation" : "/raml/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "عشاء", "answer" : "dinner", "pronunciation" : "/ʿashāʾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "نسيم", "answer" : "breeze", "pronunciation" : "/nasīm/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "قهوة", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/qahwah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "سيارة", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "/sayyārah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شرطة", "answer" : "police", "pronunciation" : "/shurṭah/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "مكتب", "answer" : "office", "pronunciation" : "/maktab/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "شاي", "answer" : "tea", "pronunciation" : "/shāy/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "كرسي", "answer" : "chair", "pronunciation" : "/kursī/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "جميل", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/jamīl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "قوي", "answer" : "strong", "pronunciation" : "/qawiyy/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "كبير", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/kabīr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "صغير", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/ṣaghīr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "جديد", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/jadīd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "قديم", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/qadīm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "عالي", "answer" : "high", "pronunciation" : "/ʿālī/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "منخفض", "answer" : "low", "pronunciation" : "/munkhafidh/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "طويل", "answer" : "long", "pronunciation" : "/ṭawīl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "قصير", "answer" : "short", "pronunciation" : "/qaṣīr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "سريع", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/sariiʿ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "بطيء", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/batiiʾ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "سهل", "answer" : "easy", "pronunciation" : "/sahl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "صعب", "answer" : "difficult", "pronunciation" : "/ṣaʿb/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "كثير", "answer" : "many", "pronunciation" : "/kathiir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "قليل", "answer" : "few", "pronunciation" : "/qaliil/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "خفيف", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "/khafiif/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ثقيل", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/thaqiil/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "غني", "answer" : "rich", "pronunciation" : "/ghaniy/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "فقير", "answer" : "poor", "pronunciation" : "/faqiir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "رائع", "answer" : "fantastic", "pronunciation" : "/raa'ii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "سيء", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/sayyiʾ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "جيد", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/jayyid/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مهم", "answer" : "important", "pronunciation" : "/mahm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "غير مهم", "answer" : "unimportant", "pronunciation" : "/ghayr mahm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "سعيد", "answer" : "happy", "pronunciation" : "/saʿiid/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "حزين", "answer" : "sad", "pronunciation" : "/ḥaziiin/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "عاطفي", "answer" : "emotional", "pronunciation" : "/ʿaatefii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "عقلاني", "answer" : "rational", "pronunciation" : "/ʿaqlaanii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مفيد", "answer" : "useful", "pronunciation" : "/mufiid/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ضار", "answer" : "harmful", "pronunciation" : "/dhaarr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "صحي", "answer" : "healthy", "pronunciation" : "/ṣahii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مريض", "answer" : "sick", "pronunciation" : "/mariidh/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ساخن", "answer" : "hot", "pronunciation" : "/saakhen/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "بارد", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "/baarid/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مرتفع", "answer" : "elevated", "pronunciation" : "/murtafiiʿ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مسطح", "answer" : "flat", "pronunciation" : "/mustaḥ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "غير مستقر", "answer" : "unstable", "pronunciation" : "/ghayr mustaqir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مستقر", "answer" : "stable", "pronunciation" : "/mustaqir/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "نظيف", "answer" : "clean", "pronunciation" : "/naẓiif/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "قذر", "answer" : "dirty", "pronunciation" : "/qadhur/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "لذيذ", "answer" : "delicious", "pronunciation" : "/ladhiidh/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "غير لذيذ", "answer" : "unpleasant", "pronunciation" : "/ghayr ladhiidh/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "مريح", "answer" : "comfortable", "pronunciation" : "/mariih/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "غير مريح", "answer" : "uncomfortable", "pronunciation" : "/ghayr mariih/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "جدير بالثناء", "answer" : "praiseworthy", "pronunciation" : "/jadhir bialthanaa'/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "الآن", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/al-ʾān/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "هناك", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/hunāka/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "هنا", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/hunā/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بعد ذلك", "answer" : "after that", "pronunciation" : "/baʿdha dhālik/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "دائمًا", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/dāʾiman/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "قريبًا", "answer" : "soon", "pronunciation" : "/qarīban/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بسرعة", "answer" : "quickly", "pronunciation" : "/bisurʿah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "لاحقًا", "answer" : "later", "pronunciation" : "/lāḥiqan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بشكل جيد", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "/bišakl jayyid/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "كثيرًا", "answer" : "much", "pronunciation" : "/kathīran/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "قليلاً", "answer" : "a little", "pronunciation" : "/qalīlan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "أحيانًا", "answer" : "sometimes", "pronunciation" : "/ʾaḥyānan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "كيفما", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/kayfamā/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "على الأرجح", "answer" : "probably", "pronunciation" : "/ʿalā al-arjaḥ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "مباشرة", "answer" : "directly", "pronunciation" : "/mubāshiratan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ببطء", "answer" : "slowly", "pronunciation" : "/bibuṭʿ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بحذر", "answer" : "carefully", "pronunciation" : "/biḥaḏr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "كل يوم", "answer" : "everyday", "pronunciation" : "/kul yawm/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "كما", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/kamā/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بشكل عام", "answer" : "generally", "pronunciation" : "/bišakl ʿām/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "دائمًا ما", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/dāʾiman mā/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بكل سهولة", "answer" : "easily", "pronunciation" : "/bikull suhūlah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بلا شك", "answer" : "undoubtedly", "pronunciation" : "/bilā šakk/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "على الأقل", "answer" : "at least", "pronunciation" : "/ʿalā al-aqall/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في كثير من الأحيان", "answer" : "often", "pronunciation" : "/fī kathīr min al-aḥyān/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في الواقع", "answer" : "actually", "pronunciation" : "/fī al-wāqiʿ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بصراحة", "answer" : "honestly", "pronunciation" : "/biṣarāḥah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في العادة", "answer" : "usually", "pronunciation" : "/fī al-ʿādah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "حتى الآن", "answer" : "until now", "pronunciation" : "/ḥattā al-ʾān/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بعناية", "answer" : "with care", "pronunciation" : "/biʿināyah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في الحقيقة", "answer" : "in fact", "pronunciation" : "/fī al-ḥaqīqah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "عمومًا", "answer" : "generally", "pronunciation" : "/ʿammuman/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في الغالب", "answer" : "mostly", "pronunciation" : "/fī al-ġālib/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "في الأساس", "answer" : "basically", "pronunciation" : "/fī al-asās/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "بلا تردد", "answer" : "without", "pronunciation" : "/bilā taraddud/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "وَ", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/wa/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "أَوْ", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/aw/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "فَ", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/fa/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "لِأَنَّ", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/li'anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بِأَنَّ", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/bi'anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "عَنْدَمَا", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/'inda ma/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "إِذَا", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/idha/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "حَتَّى", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/hatta/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "كَيْ", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/kay/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "مِثْلَ", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/mithla/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "كَمَا", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/kama/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "عَلَّى", "answer" : "on", "pronunciation" : "/alla/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "مِنْذُ", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/minzu/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "إِذْ", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/idh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بَعْدَ", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/ba'da/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "لَيْتَ", "answer" : "if only", "pronunciation" : "/layta/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "لِكَيْ", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/li-kay/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "كَأَنَّ", "answer" : "as if", "pronunciation" : "/ka'anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "حَتَّى لَا", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/hatta la/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "لِدَلِكَ", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/lidhalika/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "عَلَى أَنْ", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/ala 'an/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "طَالَمَا", "answer" : "as long as", "pronunciation" : "/talamah/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "مَعَ أَنَّ", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/ma'a anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بِمَا أَنَّ", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/bi-ma anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "كُلَّمَا", "answer" : "whenever", "pronunciation" : "/kullama/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "قَبْلَ", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "/qabla/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بَمَا أَنَّ", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/ba-ma anna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "مَثْلَمَا", "answer" : "just as", "pronunciation" : "/mithlama/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "عَمَّا", "answer" : "about", "pronunciation" : "/amma/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "حَتَّى إِذَا", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/hatta idha/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بِدَايَةِ", "answer" : "at the beginning of", "pronunciation" : "/bidayati/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "لَمَّا", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/lama/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "قُبَيْلَ", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "/qubayla/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "إِلَّا", "answer" : "except", "pronunciation" : "/illa/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "مَنْ أَنْ", "answer" : "whoever", "pronunciation" : "/man 'an/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "بَيْنَمَا", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/baynama/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "عِنْدَ", "answer" : "at", "pronunciation" : "/inda/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "حَيْثُ", "answer" : "where", "pronunciation" : "/haythu/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "دُونَ", "answer" : "below", "pronunciation" : "/dun/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]